Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
The Surprise Attack Plan
Episode 31
You’ve all come.
Thank you so much for helping me.
We will definitely support you for the sake of this place.
This is a shapeshifting device.
I need you to disguise yourselves as residents of the other world
to help me carry out the plan to retrieve the fragments.
However, this device has a time limit.
If you can’t make it back within the time limit
you’ll revert to your original forms
and they’ll see right through you.
Who among you is willing to take part in this plan?
I’ll do it.
Alright, then go on in.
The ones you’ll be impersonating
come from a world called Green Green Grassland.
Their names are Sparky and Paddi.
Hello, I’m Sparky.
Hello, I’m Paddi.
Found you at last! Come over here, quick!
What kind of place is this?
It’s so desolate here.
Wait, look over there in the distance.
Mr. Slowy, stop keeping us in suspense.
Just tell us what this place is.
This is based on data collected by drones from the rift
combined with the analysis of the monster remains we defeated earlier.
So that means
the mysterious man who’s been fighting us for the fragments is in this world.
Exactly. The rifts that appeared out of nowhere,
the multicolored fragments possessing divine magical power,
and the mysterious man who’s been sabotaging us from the shadows.
The answers we’ve been searching for might all be found here.
That’s truly great news.
We mustn’t let our guard down.
The enemy is likely figuring out how to get their hands on our fragments, too.
The real battle is just beginning.
Leave this place to us.
Right.
We need to reinforce the defenses at Goats’ Village now.
Tibbie, you and the villagers patrol inside Goats’ Village.
Okay.
I’m going to pilot a drone to infiltrate the enemy base and gather intelligence.
I won’t be able to direct the defense for a while,
and the enemy might seize the chance to invade.
Jonie, lie in wait outside the lab to keep watch,
acting as the second line of defense.
You need to speed up work on the safe
that Planie taught you to build.
Got it.
Everyone, stay at your posts.
Understood.
I heard Sparky and Paddi have found Weslie and Wolffy.
They’re on their way back.
You can always count on Slowy’s arrangements.
What’s that sound?
Sparky, Paddi—you’re back.
Yeah, Big Humphrey,
Tyger, thanks for your hard work.
You must remember the names of the residents in this world
and the relationships between them.
It wasn’t hard work; we were just guarding the gate.
By the way, where are Weslie and Wolffy?
We were just about to report on that.
Then hurry over to the lab and find him.
The plan is a success.
You look perfect; no need to worry about being found out.
Remember your ultimate objective:
to infiltrate the lab and steal the fragments.
You’re back.
This is Tibbie; she’s very sharp.
You’ll need to think on your feet—don’t blow your cover.
Hello, Tibbie.
I’m glad you’re back; Mr. Slowy is waiting for you.
Okay.
By the way, where is your gear?
O-our gear…we accidentally broke it.
We were just on our way to find Mr. Slowy for repairs.
You guys look hot.
Yeah, we ran all the way back.
Alright, then off you go.
I spotted a cockroach in the lab earlier—be careful.
It’s just a cockroach; it won’t scare us.
Exactly.
Hold it right there.
Sparky has been afraid of cockroaches since he was little. Who exactly are you?
To think someone would be afraid of cockroaches…
I never expected you to see through such a sophisticated disguise.
However…
If your mission fails in the end, then use this whistle.
That’s impossible; we’re so well-prepared.
How could anyone see through it?
Better safe than sorry.
You all come out now.
After them!
Stop!
Let us pass.
Not a chance.
Bear!
You think a ragdoll can beat us? Let’s get ’em!
Mr. Slowy, the fragment is in place.
Good. Help me here.
It’s a multicolored fragment.
This place looks unusual; I’d better take a good look around.
What are these images?
There seem to be two people over there.
Let me see who they are.
How is it…us?
What on earth is spying on us?
We finally meet.
W-w-who…who are you?
You’ve been looking for me all this time, haven’t you?
So, you’re the one responsible for creating these rifts and possessing the multicolored fragments.
I suppose so.
Why are you doing this? What exactly is your scheme?
You don’t need to know.
You just need to hand over the fragment you have to me.
In that case, we have no choice but to capture you
and force the answer out of you.
But your people have already been lured outside.
If I hadn’t done that, how else would you have shown yourself?
As long as I’m here, no one is going to hurt Mr. Slowy.
It’s a good thing Mr. Slowy had me guard the lab entrance, or I wouldn’t have spotted you sneaking in.
Facing off against you guys is getting more and more interesting.
Planie, run!
Where are you looking?
It actually came back to life.
Mr. Slowy
Don’t run.
That thing is incredibly strong.
We can’t beat it.
Run!
Let’s go.
It’s Mr. Slowy.
Hurry!
They got away.
The air on the grassland is so fresh.
Yeah, it feels good to be home.
Mr. Slowy?
What happened?
How did Goats’ Village end up like this?
Where is Mr. Slowy?
It’s all my fault; Mr. Slowy was taken away.
And the fragments were stolen, too.
To be continued